Che-Ju Lee

SUMMARY-

I studied information management for 6 years. Now, I do programing almost every day. I am a quick learner and problem solver who can handle the schoolwork and use spare time to learn programming, work and participate competition. I have ability to resolve the problem I encountered in the pass. Also I believe I can handle the challenges I will meet at work.

EDUCATION

National Cheng Kung University

2014.9 - 2016.7

Master of Information Management

Thesis: Online Consumers' Perceived Risk During Purchasing Process with Different Background on Second-hand Products: An Eye-Tracking Approach. (goo.gl/xlkhFm)

EXPERIENCE

2015.8 - 2016.7

Dept. of Physical Education, NCKU

Website Design Assistant

- Developing websites used CSS and HTML and 1 questionnaire website used php.
- Maintaining NCKU PE official issues website and the web server.

Dept. of Industrial and Information Management, NCKU

2014.9 - 2015.2

Course Assistant of Window Software Design

- Handling affairs related to the course.
- Using Dreamweaver to promote APP programming to high school students in Tainan.

PROJECT

Android Game App: Crazy Countdown

2012.9 - 2013.11

- Mainly responsible for the game UI programming. The game was developed based on eclipse, so I used the animation built in android sdk to implement battle effect.
- Using photoshop CS6 and stupeflix to make the promotion video which made nice effect.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.crazyc

HONORS

2014 Excellent prize in the International ICT Innovative Services Awards.

2014 Golden prize in the NCKU MEKTEC Competition.

2013 Excellent prize in the Information Management department.

SKILLS

Languages: ENGLISH (TOEIC 740), Mandarin.

Technical Skills: Practicing with Java(Android), Node.js and React.